Finding Aid for Luedtke Engineering Company (Frankfort, Mich.) Organizational Records
Clarke Historical Library
- Luedtke Engineering Company (Frankfort, Mich.) Organizational Records.
  - Job 657, Green Bay, WI, Griffin, Cochrane, Marshall and Elger Correspondence, 1 of 5,1987-1988 (Box 249, Folder 6)
  - Job 657, Green Bay, WI, Griffin, Cochrane, Marshall and Elger Correspondence, 2 of 5,1987-1988 (Box 250, Folder 1)
  - Job 657, Green Bay, WI, Griffin, Cochrane, Marshall and Elger Correspondence, 3 of 5,1987-1988 (Box 250, Folder 2)
  - Job 657, Green Bay, WI, Griffin, Cochrane, Marshall and Elger Correspondence, 4 of 5,1987-1988 (Box 250, Folder 3)
  - Job 657, Green Bay, WI, Griffin, Cochrane, Marshall and Elger Correspondence, 5 of 5,1987-1988 (Box 250, Folder 4)
  - Job 657, Green Bay, WI, Receipts and Estimate,1987-1990 (Box 250, Folder 5)
  - Job 658, Kewaunee, WI,1987-1988 (Box 250, Folder 6)
  - Job 658, Kewaunee, WI, Blue – line Drawings,1987 (Box 251, Folder 1)
  - Job 658, Kewaunee, WI, Bid and Estimate,1987-1988 (Box 251, Folder 2)
  - Job 658, Kewaunee, WI, Contract,1987-1988 (Box 251, Folder 3)
  - Job 658, Kewaunee, WI, Interest Claim,1987-1988 (Box 251, Folder 4)
  - Job 658, Kewaunee, WI, Photographs,undated (Box 251, Folder 5)
  - Job 659, Saginaw,1987-1988 (Box 251, Folder 6)
  - Job 659, Saginaw, Contract,1987-1988 (Box 251, Folder 7)
  - Job 659, Saginaw, Estimate,1987-1988 (Box 252, Folder 1)
  - Job 659, Saginaw, Photographs,undated (Box 252, Folder 2)
  - Job 660, Bay City,1987-1988 (Box 252, Folder 3)
  - Job 660, Bay City, Contract,1987 (Box 252, Folder 4)
  - Job 661, Detroit, 1 of 2,1987-1989 (Box 252, Folder 5)
  - Job 661, Detroit, 2 of 2,1987-1989 (Box 252, Folder 6)
  - Job 661, Detroit, Contract,1987-1988 (Box 252, Folder 7)
  - Job 661, Detroit, Drawings,1987 (Box 252, Folder 8)
  - Job 661, Detroit, Estimate,1987 (Box 252, Folder 9)
  - Job 662, Frankfort,1987-1988 (Box 253, Folder 1)
  - Job 663, Monroe,1988 (Box 253, Folder 2)
  - Job 663, Monroe, Bid,1987 (Box 253, Folder 3)
  - Job 663, Monroe, Blue – line Drawings,1987 (Box 253, Folder 4)
  - Job 663, Monroe, Contract,1988 (Box 253, Folder 5)
  - Job 663, Monroe, Photographs,1988 (Box 253, Folder 6)
  - Job 663, Monroe, Receipts and Estimate,1988 (Box 253, Folder 7)
  - Job 664, Milwaukee, WI,1988-1991 (Box 253, Folder 8)
  - Job 664, Milwaukee, WI, Bid and Estimate,1988 (Box 253, Folder 9)
  - Job 664, Milwaukee, WI, Claim,1988-1990 (Box 254, Folder 1)
  - Job 664, Milwaukee, WI, Contract, Volume 1 of 2,1987 (Box 254, Folder 2)
  - Job 664, Milwaukee, WI, Contract, Volume 2 of 2,1987 (Box 254, Folder 3)
  - Job 664, Milwaukee, WI, Correspondence,1988-1994 (Box 254, Folder 4)
  - Job 664, Milwaukee, WI, Photographs, 1 of 2,1988-1990 (Box 254, Folder 5)
  - Job 664, Milwaukee, WI, Photographs, 2 of 2,1988-1990 (Box 254, Folder 6)
  - Job 664, Milwaukee, WI, Receipts,1988-1991 (Box 255, Folder 1)
  - Job 665, Frankfort,1988 (Box 255, Folder 2)
  - Job 666, Evans, NY,1988 (Box 255, Folder 3)
  - Job 666, Evans, NY, Blue – line Drawings, 1 of 2,1987 (Box 255, Folder 4)
  - Job 666, Evans, NY, Blue – line Drawings, 2 of 2,1987 (Box 255, Folder 5)
  - Job 666, Evans, NY, Contract,1988 (Box 256, Folder 1)
  - Job 666, Evans, NY, Negatives,undated (Box 256, Folder 2)
  - Job 666, Evans, NY, Orders and Estimate,1988 (Box 256, Folder 3)
  - Job 666, Evans, NY, Photographs,1988 (Box 256, Folder 4)
  - Job 666, Evans, NY, Selvick Marine Correspondence, 1 of 2,1988 (Box 256, Folder 5)
  - Job 666, Evans, NY, Selvick Marine Correspondence, 2 of 2,1988 (Box 256, Folder 6)
  - Job 667, Frankfort,1988-1989 (Box 257, Folder 1)
  - Job 668, Gary, IN,1989 (Box 257, Folder 2)
  - Job 668, Gary, IN, Contract, Receipts and Estimate,1989 (Box 257, Folder 3)
  - Job 668, Gary, IN, Photographs,undated (Box 257, Folder 4)
  - Job 669, Waukegan, IL,1988 (Box 257, Folder 5)
  - Job 669, Waukegan, IL, Specifications,1988 (Box 257, Folder 6)
  - Job 670, Waukegan, IL,1988 (Box 257, Folder 7)
  - Job 670, Waukegan, IL, Photographs,1988 (Box 257, Folder 8)
  - Job 671, Buffalo, NY,1988 (Box 257, Folder 9)
  - Job 671, Buffalo, NY, Blue – line Drawings,1988 (Box 258, Folder 1)
  - Job 671, Buffalo, NY, Con Agra Correspondence,1988 (Box 258, Folder 2)
  - Job 671, Buffalo, NY, Con Agra Photographs,1988 (Box 258, Folder 3)
  - Job 671, Buffalo, NY, Contract,1988 (Box 258, Folder 4)
  - Job 671, Buffalo, NY, Correspondence,1988 (Box 258, Folder 5)
  - Job 671, Buffalo, NY, Drawings,1988 (Box 258, Folder 6)
  - Job 671, Buffalo, NY, Photographs,1988 (Box 258, Folder 7)
  - Job 671, Buffalo, NY, Receipts, Estimate and Orders,1988 (Box 258, Folder 8)
  - Job 672, Holland, 1 of 2,1988 – 1990 (Box 258, Folder 9)
  - Job 672, Holland, 2 of 2,1988 – 1990 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Job 672, Holland, Bid and Estimate,1988 – 1989 (Box 259, Folder 1)
  - Job 672, Holland, Bid Instructions,1988 (Box 259, Folder 2)
  - Job 672, Holland, Blue – line Drawings,1988 (Box 259, Folder 3)
  - Job 672, Holland, Contract,1988 (Box 259, Folder 4)
  - Job 672, Holland, Claim,1988-1989 (Box 259, Folder 5)
  - Job 672, Holland, Correspondence, 1 of 2,1988-1989 (Box 259, Folder 6)
  - Job 672, Holland, Correspondence, 2 of 2,1988-1989 (Box 260, Folder 1)
  - Job 672, Holland, Drawings,1988-1989 (Box 260, Folder 2)
  - Job 672, Holland, Orders,1988-1989 (Box 260, Folder 3)
  - Job 672, Holland, Payment Estimate,1988-1990 (Box 260, Folder 4)
  - Job 672, Holland, Photographs,Undated (Box 260, Folder 5)
  - Job 673, Charlevoix,1988-1989 (Box 260, Folder 6)
  - Job 673, Charlevoix, Bid and Estimate,1988 (Box 260, Folder 7)
  - Job 673, Charlevoix, Bid Instructions,1988 (Box 261, Folder 1)
  - Job 673, Charlevoix, Contract,1988-1990 (Box 261, Folder 2)
  - Job 673, Charlevoix, Drawings, 1 of 2,1988 (Box 261, Folder 3)
  - Job 673, Charlevoix, Drawings, 2 of 2,1988 (Box 261, Folder 4)
  - Job 673, Charlevoix, Grout Problem,1990 (Box 261, Folder 5)
  - Job 673, Charlevoix, Orders,1988 – 1989 (Box 261, Folder 6)
  - Job 673, Charlevoix, Payment Estimate, 1 of 2,1988 – 1989 (Box 262, Folder 1)
  - Job 673, Charlevoix, Payment Estimate, 2 of 2,1988 – 1989 (Box 262, Folder 2)
  - Job 673, Charlevoix, Photographs,Undated (Box 262, Folder 3)
  - Job 674, West Harbor, OH,1988 (Box 262, Folder 4)
  - Job 673, Charlevoix, Claims,1988-1989 (Box 262, Folder 5)
  - Job 673, Charlevoix, Contracts,1988 (Box 262, Folder 6)
  - Job 673, Charlevoix, Drawings,1988-1989 (Box 262, Folder 7)
  - Job 673, Charlevoix, Receipts and Estimate,1988 (Box 262, Folder 8)
  - Job 675, Frankfort,1988 (Box 263, Folder 1)
  - Job 675, Frankfort, Correspondence and Estimate,1988 (Box 263, Folder 2)
  - Job 675, Frankfort, Drawings,1988 (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Job 675, Frankfort, Specifications,1989 (Box 263, Folder 4)
  - Job 676, Erie, PA,1988 (Box 263, Folder 5)
  - Job 676, Erie, PA, Contract,1988 (Box 263, Folder 6)
  - Job 677, Leland,1989 (Box 263, Folder 7)
  - Job 677, Leland, Blue – line Drawings,1988 (Box 263, Folder 8)
  - Job 677, Leland, Contract,1988 (Box 263, Folder 9)
  - Job 677, Leland, Receipts and Estimate,1988 (Box 264, Folder 1)
  - Job 678, Manistee,1989 (Box 264, Folder 2)
  - Job 678, Manistee, Bid,1989 (Box 264, Folder 3)
  - Job 678, Manistee, Contract, Receipts and Estimate,1989 (Box 264, Folder 4)
  - Job 679, Erie, PA,1989 (Box 264, Folder 5)
  - Job 679, Erie, PA, Claim,1989 (Box 264, Folder 6)
  - Job 679, Erie, PA, Contract and Estimate, 1 of 2,1989 (Box 264, Folder 7)
  - Job 679, Erie, PA, Contract and Estimate, 2 of 2,1989 (Box 264, Folder 8)
  - Job 679, Erie, PA, Correspondence,1989 (Box 265, Folder 1)
  - Job 679, Erie, PA, Drawings,1989 (Box 265, Folder 2)
  - Job 679, Erie, PA, McKinney Drilling Correspondence,1989 (Box 265, Folder 3)
  - Job 679, Erie, PA, Photographs,Undated (Box 265, Folder 4)
  - Job 679, Erie, PA, Specifications,1989 (Box 265, Folder 5)
  - Job 679, Erie, PA, Top Roc Lawsuit, Official Correspondence,1989-1993 (Box 265, Folder 6)
  - Job 679, Erie, PA, Top Roc Lawsuit, Final Correspondence,1993-1994 (Box 265, Folder 7)
  - Job 679, Erie, PA, Top Roc Lawsuit, Trail Exhibits, 1 of 2,1989 (Box 266, Folder 1)
  - Job 679, Erie, PA, Top Roc Lawsuit, Trail Exhibits, 2 of 2,1989 (Box 266, Folder 2)
  - Job 680, Monroe,1988 – 1989 (Box 266, Folder 3)
  - Job 680, Monroe, Bid Instructions,1989 (Box 266, Folder 4)
  - Job 680, Monroe, Contract,1989 (Box 266, Folder 5)
  - Job 681, Fairport, OH,1989 (Box 266, Folder 6)
  - Job 682, St. Joseph,1989 (Box 266, Folder 7)
  - Job 682, St. Joseph, Contract,1989 (Box 266, Folder 8)
  - Job 683, St. Joseph,1988 – 1991 (Box 267, Folder 1)
  - Job 683, St. Joseph, Contract,1990 (Box 267, Folder 2)
  - Job 683, St. Joseph, Correspondence,1989 – 1991 (Box 267, Folder 3)
  - Job 683, St. Joseph, Drawings,1989 – 1990 (Box 267, Folder 4)
  - Job 683, St. Joseph, Estimate and Design Calculations,1988 (Box 267, Folder 5)
  - Job 683, St. Joseph, Orders,1990-1991 (Box 267, Folder 6)
  - Job 683, St. Joseph, Permits,1988-1990 (Box 267, Folder 7)
  - Job 683, St. Joseph, Photographs,Undated (Box 267, Folder 8)
  - Job 683, St. Joseph, Specifications,1989-1990 (Box 267, Folder 9)
  - Job 684, Michigan City, IN,1989 (Box 268, Folder 1)
  - Job 684, Michigan City, IN, Contract,1989 (Box 268, Folder 2)
  - Job 684, Michigan City, IN, Drawings,1989 (Box 268, Folder 3)
  - Job 684, Michigan City, IN, Specifications,1989 (Box 268, Folder 4)
  - Job 685, Filer City,1989-1990 (Box 268, Folder 5)
  - Job 686, Evanston, IL,1989 (Box 268, Folder 6)
  - Job 686, Evanston, IL, Blue – line Drawings, 1 of 2,1989 (Box 268, Folder 7)
  - Job 686, Evanston, IL, Blue – line Drawings, 2 of 2,1989 (Box 269, Folder 1)
  - Job 686, Evanston, IL, Contract,1989 (Box 269, Folder 2)
  - Job 686, Evanston, IL, Correspondence, 1 of 2,1989-1990 (Box 269, Folder 3)
  - Job 686, Evanston, IL, Correspondence, 2 of 2,1989-1990 (Box 269, Folder 4)
  - Job 686, Evanston, IL, Drawings, 1 of 2,1989 (Box 269, Folder 5)
  - Job 686, Evanston, IL, Drawings, 2 of 2,1989 (Box 269, Folder 6)
  - Job 686, Evanston, IL, Gillen Co. Correspondence,1989 (Box 270, Folder 1)
  - Job 686, Evanston, IL, Negatives,1989 (Box 270, Folder 2)
  - Job 686, Evanston, IL, Orders,1989 (Box 270, Folder 3)
  - Job 686, Evanston, IL, Photographs, 1 of 2,1989 (Box 270, Folder 4)
  - Job 686, Evanston, IL, Photographs, 2 of 2,1989 (Box 270, Folder 5)
  - Job 686, Evanston, IL, Progressive Fabricators Correspondence,1989 (Box 270, Folder 6)
  - Job 686, Evanston, IL, Receipts and Estimate,1989-1990 (Box 271, Folder 1)
  - Job 686, Evanston, IL, Specifications,1989 (Box 271, Folder 2)
  - Job 687, Eastlake, OH,1989 (Box 271, Folder 3)
  - Job 687, Eastlake, OH, Contract and Specifications,1989 (Box 271, Folder 4)
  - Job 688, Hammond, IN,1989-1991 (Box 271, Folder 5)
  - Job 688, Hammond, IN, Blue – line Drawings, 1 of 2,1989 (Box 271, Folder 6)
  - Job 688, Hammond, IN, Blue – line Drawings, 2 of 2,1989 (Box 271, Folder 7)
  - Job 688, Hammond, IN, Contract,1989 (Box 272, Folder 1)
  - Job 688, Hammond, IN, Photographs,Undated (Box 272, Folder 2)
  - Job 691, Bay Village, OH,1989 – 1992 (Box 272, Folder 3)
  - Job 691, Bay Village, OH, Contract,1989 – 1990 (Box 272, Folder 4)
  - Job 691, Bay Village, OH, Drawings, 1 of 2,1989 (Box 272, Folder 5)
  - Job 691, Bay Village, OH, Drawings, 2 of 2,1989 (Box 272, Folder 6)
  - Job 691, Bay Village, OH, Estimate,1989 (Box 273, Folder 1)
  - Job 691, Bay Village, OH, Orders,1989 (Box 273, Folder 2)
  - Job 691, Bay Village, OH, Receipts,1989-1991 (Box 273, Folder 3)
  - Job 691, Bay Village, OH, Specifications,1989 (Box 273, Folder 4)
  - Job 692, Rock Island, IL, 1 of 2,1989-1990 (Box 273, Folder 5)
  - Job 692, Rock Island, IL, 2 of 2,1989-1990 (Box 273, Folder 6)
  - Job 692, Rock Island, IL, Bid, Estimate and Contract,1989-1990 (Box 273, Folder 7)
  - Job 692, Rock Island, IL, Photographs,Undated (Box 273, Folder 8)
  - Job 692, Rock Island, IL, Specifications,1989 (Box 273, Folder 9)
  - Job 693, Milwaukee, WI,1989-1990 (Box 274, Folder 1)
  - Job 694, Ontonagon,1990 (Box 274, Folder 2)
  - Job 694, Ontonagon, Bid, Estimate and Contract,1989-1990 (Box 274, Folder 3)
  - Job 694, Ontonagon, Specifications,1990 (Box 274, Folder 4)
  - Job 695, Ashtabula, OH,1990 (Box 274, Folder 5)
  - Job 696, Green Bay, WI,1990 (Box 274, Folder 6)
  - Job 697, Frankfort,1990-1991 (Box 274, Folder 7)
  - Job 698, Lorain, OH,1989-1990 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Job 699, Port Austin,1990 (Box 274, Folder 9)
  - Job 699, Port Austin, Blue-line Drawings,1990 (Box 274, Folder 10)
  - Job 699, Port Austin, Contract and Correspondence and Estimate,1990 (Box 275, Folder 1)
  - Job 699, Port Austin, Correspondence,1990 (Box 275, Folder 2)
  - Job 700, Suttons Bay,1990 (Box 275, Folder 3)
  - Job 700, Suttons Bay, Blue-line Drawings,1990 (Box 275, Folder 4)
  - Job 700, Suttons Bay, Claim,1990 (Box 275, Folder 5)
  - Job 700, Suttons Bay, Correspondence,1990 (Box 275, Folder 6)
  - Job 701, Buffalo, NY,1990 (Box 275, Folder 7)
  - Job 701, Buffalo, NY, Bid,1990 (Box 275, Folder 8)
  - Job 701, Buffalo, NY, Contract,1990 (Box 276, Folder 1)
  - Job 701, Buffalo, NY, Photographs,1990 (Box 276, Folder 2)
  - Job 701, Buffalo, NY, Receipts and Estimate,1990-1992 (Box 276, Folder 3)
  - Job 702, Milwaukee, WI,1990 (Box 276, Folder 4)
  - Job 702, Milwaukee, WI, Blue-line Drawings,1990 (Box 276, Folder 5)
  - Job 702, Milwaukee, WI, Contract,1990 (Box 276, Folder 6)
  - Job 703, Cleveland, OH,1990 (Box 276, Folder 7)
  - Job 703, Cleveland, OH, Bid and Estimate,1990 (Box 276, Folder 8)
  - Job 703, Cleveland, OH, Blue-line Drawings, 1 of 2,1991 (Box 277, Folder 1)
  - Job 703, Cleveland, OH, Blue-line Drawings, 2 of 2,1991 (Box 277, Folder 2)
  - Job 703, Cleveland, OH, Contract Correspondence,1991 (Box 277, Folder 3)
  - Job 703, Cleveland, OH, Correspondence,1991 (Box 277, Folder 4)
  - Job 703, Cleveland, OH, Drawings,1991 (Box 277, Folder 5)
  - Job 703, Cleveland, OH, Orders and Receipts,1991 (Box 277, Folder 6)
  - Job 703, Cleveland, OH, Photographs, 1 of 2,1990 (Box 278, Folder 1)
  - Job 703, Cleveland, OH, Photographs, 2 of 2,1990 (Box 278, Folder 2)
  - Job 703, Cleveland, OH, Roth Manufacturing Corp. Correspondence,1991 (Box 278, Folder 3)
  - Job 703, Cleveland, OH, Specifications,1991 (Box 278, Folder 4)
  - Job 704, Tonawanda, NY,1990-1991 (Box 278, Folder 5)
  - Job 704, Tonawanda, NY, Bid, Estimate, and Cost Sheets,1991 (Box 278, Folder 6)
  - Job 704, Tonawanda, NY, Blue-line Drawings, 1 of 2,1991 (Box 278, Folder 7)
  - Job 704, Tonawanda, NY, Blue-line Drawings, 2 of 2,1991 (Box 279, Folder 1)
  - Job 704, Tonawanda, NY, Correspondence, 1 of 2,1991 (Box 279, Folder 2)
  - Job 704, Tonawanda, NY, Correspondence, 2 of 2,1991 (Box 279, Folder 3)
  - Job 704, Tonawanda, NY, County of Erie Contract Correspondence,1 of 4,1991 (Box 279, Folder 4)
  - Job 704, Tonawanda, NY, County of Erie Contract Correspondence, 2 of 4,1991 (Box 279, Folder 5)
  - Job 704, Tonawanda, NY, County of Erie Contract Correspondence, 3 of 4,1991 (Box 280, Folder 1)
  - Job 704, Tonawanda, NY, County of Erie Contract Correspondence, 4 of 4,1991 (Box 280, Folder 2)
  - Job 704, Tonawanda, NY, Drawings,1991 (Box 280, Folder 3)
  - Job 704, Tonawanda, NY, Orders and Receipts,1991 (Box 280, Folder 4)
  - Job 704, Tonawanda, NY, Photographs,1991 (Box 280, Folder 5)
  - Job 705, Rochester, NY,1990-1992 (Box 280, Folder 6)
  - Job 705, Rochester, NY, Bid and Estimate,1990-1991 (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Job 705, Rochester, NY, Blue-line Drawings, 1 of 2,1990 (Box 281, Folder 2)
  - Job 705, Rochester, NY, Blue-line Drawings, 2 of 2,1990 (Box 281, Folder 3)
  - Job 705, Rochester, NY, Claims, 1 of 2,1991 (Box 281, Folder 4)
  - Job 705, Rochester, NY, Claims, 2 of 2,1991 (Box 281, Folder 5)
  - Job 705, Rochester, NY, Contract Correspondence, 1 of 2,1990-1991 (Box 281, Folder 7)
  - Job 705, Rochester, NY, Contract Correspondence, 2 of 2,1990-1991 (Box 281, Folder 8)
  - Job 705, Rochester, NY, Correspondence, 1 of 2,1991 (Box 282, Folder 1)
  - Job 705, Rochester, NY, Correspondence, 2 of 2,1991 (Box 282, Folder 2)
  - Job 705, Rochester, NY, C.P. Ward Correspondence,1990-1991 (Box 282, Folder 3)
  - Job 705, Rochester, NY, Orders and Receipts,1990-1991 (Box 282, Folder 4)
  - Job 705, Rochester, NY, Photographs,1990-1991 (Box 282, Folder 5)
  - Job 705, Rochester, NY, Quality Control,1990-1992 (Box 282, Folder 6)
  - Job 705, Rochester, NY, Quotes,1990 (Box 282, Folder 7)
  - Job 705, Rochester, NY, Transmittals,1990-1991 (Box 283, Folder 1)
  - Job 706, Painesville, OH,1990-1992 (Box 283, Folder 2)
  - Job 706, Painesville, OH, Blue-line Drawings, 1 of 2,1989-1990 (Box 283, Folder 3)
  - Job 706, Painesville, OH, Blue-line Drawings, 2 of 2,1989-1990 (Box 283, Folder 4)
  - Job 706, Painesville, OH, Contract Specifications,1990 (Box 283, Folder 5)
  - Job 706, Painesville, OH, Correspondence,1990-1992 (Box 283, Folder 6)
  - Job 706, Painesville, OH, Estimate,1990 (Box 283, Folder 7)
  - Job 706, Painesville, OH, Norfolk Southern Correspondence,1990 (Box 284, Folder 1)
  - Job 706, Painesville, OH, Orders,1990-1991 (Box 284, Folder 2)
  - Job 706, Painesville, OH, Photographs, 1 of 3,1990 (Box 284, Folder 3)
  - Job 706, Painesville, OH, Photographs, 2 of 3,1990 (Box 284, Folder 4)
  - Job 706, Painesville, OH, Photographs, 3 of 3,1990 (Box 284, Folder 5)
  - Job 706, Painesville, OH, Quantities,1992 (Box 284, Folder 6)
  - Job 706, Painesville, OH, Quotation,1990 (Box 284, Folder 7)
  - Job 706, Painesville, OH, Receipts, 1 of 2,1990 (Box 285, Folder 1)
  - Job 706, Painesville, OH, Receipts, 2 of 2,1990 (Box 285, Folder 2)
  - Job 707, Presque Isle,1990-1991 (Box 285, Folder 3)
  - Job 707, Presque Isle, Blue-line Drawings, 1 of 3,1990 (Box 285, Folder 4)
  - Job 707, Presque Isle, Blue-line Drawings, 2 of 3,1990 (Box 285, Folder 5)
  - Job 707, Presque Isle, Blue-line Drawings, 3 of 3,1990 (Box 285, Folder 6)
  - Job 707, Presque Isle, Contract, 1 of 2,1990 (Box 286, Folder 1)
  - Job 707, Presque Isle, Contract, 2 of 2,1990 (Box 286, Folder 2)
  - Job 707, Presque Isle, Correspondence,1990-1992 (Box 286, Folder 3)
  - Job 707, Presque Isle, Cross Concrete Pumping Correspondence,1991 (Box 286, Folder 4)
  - Job 707, Presque Isle, Orders, Receipts and Estimates,1991 (Box 286, Folder 5)
  - Job 707, Presque Isle, Photographs,1990 (Box 286, Folder 6)
  - Job 708, Petoskey,1990-1991 (Box 286, Folder 7)
  - Job 708, Petoskey, Blue-line Drawings, 1 of 2,1991 (Box 287, Folder 1)
  - Job 708, Petoskey, Blue-line Drawings, 2 of 2,1991 (Box 287, Folder 2)
  - Job 708, Petoskey, Contract Correspondence,1991 (Box 287, Folder 3)
  - Job 708, Petoskey, Correspondence,1991 (Box 287, Folder 4)
  - Job 708, Petoskey, Estimate and Bidding papers,1991 (Box 287, Folder 5)
  - Job 708, Petoskey, Final As-builts and Report,1990 (Box 287, Folder 6)
  - Job 708, Petoskey, Photographs,1990 (Box 288, Folder 1)
  - Job 708, Petoskey, Quotations,1990 (Box 288, Folder 2)
  - Job 708, Petoskey, Receipts and Orders,1991 (Box 288, Folder 3)
  - Job 708, Petoskey, Specifications,1990 (Box 288, Folder 4)
  - Job 709, Illinois Waterway, IL,1991 (Box 288, Folder 5)
  - Job 709, Illinois Waterway, IL, Bid and Contract,1991 (Box 288, Folder 6)
  - Job 709, Illinois Waterway, IL, Estimate and Quotes,1991 (Box 288, Folder 7)
  - Job 709, Illinois Waterway, IL, Orders and Receipts,1991-1992 (Box 289, Folder 1)
  - Job 709, Illinois Waterway, IL, Photographs,1991 (Box 289, Folder 2)
  - Job 710, Sandusky, OH,1991 (Box 289, Folder 3)
  - Job 710, Sandusky, OH, Contract Correspondence and Bid,1991 (Box 289, Folder 4)
  - Job 710, Sandusky, OH, Correspondence,1991-1992 (Box 289, Folder 5)
  - Job 710, Sandusky, OH, Orders and Estimate,1991 (Box 289, Folder 6)
  - Job 711, Gulliver,1991 (Box 289, Folder 7)
  - Job 711, Gulliver, Specifications and Estimate,1991 (Box 289, Folder 8)
  - Job 712, Frankfort,1991 (Box 290, Folder 1)
  - Job 713, Fairport Harbor, OH,1991 (Box 290, Folder 2)
  - Job 713, Fairport Harbor, OH, Bid,1991 (Box 290, Folder 3)
  - Job 713, Fairport Harbor, OH, Contract,1991-1992 (Box 290, Folder 4)
  - Job 713, Fairport Harbor, OH, Correspondence,1991 (Box 290, Folder 5)
  - Job 713, Fairport Harbor, OH, Estimate and Receipts,1991 (Box 290, Folder 6)
  - Job 714, Buffalo, NY,1991 (Box 290, Folder 7)
  - Job 714, Buffalo, NY, Bid,1991 (Box 290, Folder 8)
  - Job 714, Buffalo, NY, Blue-line Drawings,1988-1991 (Box 290, Folder 9)
  - Job 714, Buffalo, NY, ConAgra Correspondence,1991 (Box 290, Folder 10)
  - Job 714, Buffalo, NY, Contract,1991 (Box 291, Folder 1)
  - Job 714, Buffalo, NY, Orders and Receipts,1991 (Box 291, Folder 2)
  - Job 714, Buffalo, NY, Photographs,1991 (Box 291, Folder 3)
  - Job 715, Marblehead, OH,1991 (Box 291, Folder 4)
  - Job 715, Marblehead, OH, Blue-line Drawings,1991 (Box 291, Folder 5)
  - Job 715, Marblehead, OH, Estimate and Receipts,1991 (Box 291, Folder 6)
  - Job 716, Fairport, OH,1991 (Box 291, Folder 7)
  - Job 717, Toussaint River, OH,1991 (Box 291, Folder 8)
  - Job 717, Toussaint River, OH, Blue-line Drawings,1991 (Box 291, Folder 9)
  - Job 717, Toussaint River, OH, Claim,1991 (Box 291, Folder 10)
  - Job 717, Toussaint River, OH, Photographs,1991 (Box 292, Folder 1)
  - Job 717, Toussaint River, OH, Receipts and Estimate,1991 (Box 292, Folder 2)
  - Job 717, Toussaint River, OH, Specifications,1991 (Box 292, Folder 3)
  - Job 718, Cleveland, OH,1991-1992 (Box 292, Folder 4)
  - Job 718, Cleveland, OH, Bid and Estimate,1991 (Box 292, Folder 5)
  - Job 718, Cleveland, OH, Blue-line Drawings, 1 of 2,1991 (Box 292, Folder 6)
  - Job 718, Cleveland, OH, Blue-line Drawings, 2 of 2,1991 (Box 292, Folder 7)
  - Job 718, Cleveland, OH, Contract, 1 of 2,1991 (Box 292, Folder 8)
  - Job 718, Cleveland, OH, Contract, 2 of 2,1991 (Box 292, Folder 9)
  - Job 718, Cleveland, OH, Correspondence,1991-1992 (Box 293, Folder 1)
  - Job 718, Cleveland, OH, Orders and Receipts,1991-1993 (Box 293, Folder 2)
  - Job 718, Cleveland, OH, Photographs,1991 (Box 293, Folder 3)
  - Job 719, Clinton River,1991 (Box 293, Folder 4)
  - Job 719, Clinton River, Bid,1991 (Box 293, Folder 5)
  - Job 719, Clinton River, Blue-line Drawings,1991 (Box 293, Folder 6)
  - Job 719, Clinton River, Contract and Estimate,1991-1992 (Box 293, Folder 7)
  - Job 719, Clinton River, Correspondence, 1 of 2,1991-1993 (Box 294, Folder 1)
  - Job 719, Clinton River, Correspondence, 2 of 2,1991-1993 (Box 294, Folder 2)
  - Job 719, Clinton River, Claim,1991 (Box 294, Folder 3)
  - Job 719, Clinton River, Order and Receipts,1991-1992 (Box 294, Folder 4)
  - Job 720, Lorain, OH,1991 (Box 294, Folder 5)
  - Job 721 Ashtabula, OH,1991 (Box 294, Folder 6)
  - Job 722, Charlevoix,1991-1992 (Box 294, Folder 7)
  - Job 722, Charlevoix, Bid and Specifications,1991 (Box 294, Folder 8)
  - Job 722, Charlevoix, Contract,1992 (Box 295, Folder 1)
  - Job 722, Charlevoix, Correspondence,1992 (Box 295, Folder 2)
  - Job 722, Charlevoix, Orders and Receipts,1991-1992 (Box 295, Folder 3)
  - Job 723, Ludington,1992 (Box 295, Folder 4)
  - Job 723, Ludington, Contract,1992 (Box 295, Folder 5)
  - Job 724, Gulliver,1992 (Box 295, Folder 6)
  - Job 724, Gulliver, Blue-line Drawings,1992 (Box 295, Folder 7)
  - Job 724, Gulliver, Specifications and Estimate,1991 (Box 295, Folder 8)
  - Job 725, Frankfort,1992 (Box 295, Folder 9)
  - Job 725, Frankfort, Hallmark Construction and Koch Materials Correspondence,1992 (Box 296, Folder 1)
  - Job 726, Harbor Beach,1992 (Box 296, Folder 2)
  - Job 726, Harbor Beach, Bid,1992 (Box 296, Folder 3)
  - Job 726, Harbor Beach, Contract and Receipts,1992 (Box 296, Folder 4)
  - Job 727, Rochester, NY,1992 (Box 296, Folder 5)
  - Job 727, Rochester, NY, Bid,1992 (Box 296, Folder 6)
  - Job 727, Rochester, NY, Contract and Receipts,1992 (Box 296, Folder 7)